# Resume of Don Nisnoni

# **SUMMARY**

Don is a passionate, motivated, and creative web developer with work experience since 2020. He learning web development since 2015 and mostly focused on front-end web development but has the flexibility and experience to work on back-end web development as well. He experience with web technologies and tools such as NodeJS, MySQL, PHP, Laravel, ReactJS, and VueJS.

# **PERSONAL DATA**

Age: 26 years old

Occupation: Kuta, Bali - Indonesia

Phone: <u>+6283809705594</u> or via <u>WhatsApp</u> Email: <u>donalfonsnnisnoni@gmail.com</u> Personal Website: <u>donnisnoni.github.io</u>

GitHub: <u>donnisnoni</u> LinkedIn: <u>donnisnoni</u>

# **EDUCATION**

Associate Degree of Information Technology at STIKOM UYELINDO Kupang

Jul 2015 - Dec 2019 - GPA: 3.44

# **SKILLS**

Thing's that I've touch so far:

# Software/Tools:

Git, GitHub, Docker, Netlify, Vercel, PostCSS, Hugo SSG, Discourse

#### Databases:

Redis, MySQL & MariaDB

#### **Programming Languages:**

HTML, CSS, Javascript, NodeJS, Typescript, C#, V, SASS, SQL, PHP, Python

# Frameworks/Libraries:

jQuery, Vue, React, Svelte, Sapper, Codelgniter, Laravel, Express, Fastify, Sequelize, TailwindCSS

# Technique:

December Web Decide 1114 i105 DWA

# **EXPERIENCES**

# Web Developer & IT Support

Feb 2020 - Aug 2020 at STIKOM UYELINDO Kupang

- Build a website for improve student's online services.
- Upgrade & improve campus main website.
- Analyze and improve existing campus websites security and UI.
- Upgrade campus tech stacks.

#### Part-time Front-End Web Developer

Feb 2021 - May 2021 at **Vlingo** 

• Implementing <u>vlingo/auth</u> UI using SvelteKit framework.

# Full-time Front-End Web Developer

May 2021 - Present at Alphien SAS

- Building and maintain NuxtJS and VueJS websites.
- Building and maintain Laravel websites.
- Extending a discourse forum (Develop discourse widgets and extensions).
- Develop JupyterLab extensions.

Don Alfons Nisnoni